so we were discussing the other day
about themes which is commonly translate
well it's the Hollywood is limiter which
are usually used to themes right but
it's signs signs and features signs and
tokens characteristics so English themes
yeah it doesn't quite correspond to
limiter but it's certainly related so
I'm interested in it idea of developing
certain themes you know for calming the
matter is that Souter says develop
Samadhi new meter write the theme of
composure right in the morning so you
have to take a particular theme develop
it maintain it
okay yeah well in that sense themit's
it's a good it's a good word good
practice as well it's what I was
referring in previous some previous
talks as context as well to establish
your mind upon a certain theme doesn't
mean you hold that theme as a as a some
sort of mental object means actually you
discern it as a as a as a base as a
basis in in form of a context as a basis
for your action so you want to develop
theme that was going to again D give the
overall mood to your experience or
direction towards your experience so so
if your theme gives direction like yeah
exactly direct that's what that's when in
direct that's what that's when in
context like context already oh so these
actions are against the backdrop of a
certain context so if that context is
context it's it's free from greed free
from free from lust and desire free from
a version free from distraction means no
particular actions would be able to
partake in that nature that this context
is free from and that's why that's what
that responsible that I mean it's not a
meditation object that you just sort of
ponder on it's something you need to
actively think about establish it and
then it's effortless then you only need
to maintain it and that's the basic
practice practice of mindfulness it's
done correctly
rather than doing things which you think
are free from anger even lust
yes before division I'll do yeah that's
like that's looking at the opposite
direction of the context of the theme
you are looking or if I go through these
motions I will I will somehow evoke the
theme I'm supposed to have but the only
way to truly establish a theme is to
discern what that theme is so by
dwelling on the context under limiters
the characteristics of the context you
get to familiarize yourself in the
context is and then you see that your
particular behavior is under the
influence of the context that you
established so if your context is
context of constant careless sensuality
careless speech means your actions will
be reflecting that context
it will be directed by the context by
the theme of carelessness by the theme
of lust and greed but if you just hope
to mechanically induce it it won't work
because again all you are focusing on is
the particular actions so although your
softly spoken and moving very slowly and
you're just emulating what you think
should be coming out of the context of
calmness and context of non your will
but if you actually get a context you
don't need to waste an effort emulating
it because you have it why would you be
pretending it to have it when you have
it you can't get the content and then
even if your actions don't necessarily
mirror what you thought you should have
been acting like from the context of non
lwill you know there is no your will
because you discern the context of
narnia well you haven't just blindly
emulated and went through the motions
and techniques of narnia will same with
lovingkindness same with anything any
any anything and that's why mindfulness
is done rightly results in wisdom to see
you have to discern the context you have
to understand the context the theme
same with jhanas that's what i'm going
to say he if a monk doesn't if he
doesn't well if he doesn't invest effort
in developing the theme of jhana which
means he already has discerned the theme
but now he needs to invest the effort
and develop that theme if he doesn't do
so he's like a mountain car that you
know as soon as he steps on one stone
thinks about the next and doesn't get
stable on any and falls in between so
even with jhanas even with samadhi with
composure you actually want to develop
the theme of composure discern it and
then develop it which means you mustn't
overshoot the mark no must you
understood it so to speak
so for example the developing mind of
loving-kindness you could you could take
a course that's right bit sunny yeah I
think it's gonna come behind the
branches soon so developing a mind of
loving-kindness you could go on a course you think what
you could go on a course you think what
does a person look like or what is a
person with loving-kindness Duke well
he's softly spoken hmm people liking
these speaks Chinese good in
communication so then you decide I will
take a communication course in
nonviolent communication yeah so that I
can do better
this special mind of loving-kindness and
so you do this course but trying to see
that you even if you don't necessarily
have your will as long as you don't
discern the phenomena of the theme of
loving-kindness means all your going to
be doing focusing on the particular
aspects of your behavior and they should
be coming out of loving kindness not
inducing loving kindness it doesn't work
that way so yeah if you dwell on
someone's behavior and discern certain
traits so that you can understand the
context behind that's fine but it's when
people don't look behind
they don't look peripherally to see what
gives meaning to these actions they just
hope if I go through the motions of
these actions I will have the same
result as this other person that is
seemingly acting out of loving kindness
and that's that's a wrong order of
things and that's why those people will
struggle then reconciling like certain
behaviors of an arahant they don't fit
with the preconceived notion of how
other hand should be mechanically acting
and that's that those are the cases in
the sutras when the Buddha said no you
know he might have been roughly you know
speaking roughly and so on but things
that are hand can't do at things of
sensual nature things that were world
but all the other things that just can
be also attributed to various habits and
and those are not the criteria so the
little like
little little little little kind of
patterns of your behavior and if you're
investing effort in that means you don't
know where the problem is the problem is
you being bound by the context of
ignorance bound by the context of lust
a version conceit self-centeredness by
by the context of Abaddonn a context of
assumptions and because you don't see
that you think that refining your
behavior and learning how to speak
slowly and walk slowly you are somehow
contributing to its purification you
know you're actually trying to deal with
the problem where problem isn't like
speaking harshly and so on are usually
the symptoms of the problem of the
context to fill will but if you just
keep refining the symptoms you all you
do is basically refabricate in the way
that it will will reexpress itself it's
gonna find some other way of expressing
as in you know imagine a person speaking
very softly but with fuming on the
inside but if you actually that's why I
got a never talked about like you go
around and sort of deal with this to
deal with that he would always refer to
uprooting the problem so you are plotted
then you don't have to deal with any of
these little things and manifestations
of it because there's nothing fueling it
which means they cease to be the
symptoms first thing you don't have to
develop physical skills no as far as
development of physical skills goes it's
the Vinaya sila five precept eight three
sips temperatures whatever you keep me
though that is the physical physical
emulation of certain behavior Nonya will
non-centrality not lying not stealing
not killing not cheating and so on but
everything else on top of that will only
be right if it's seen from the point of
view of the right context of the right
theme
and if you realize that to work isn't
there in the mind that you need to sort
out yes cleaning the Maya a lot of you
can save yourself a lot of time oh you
can see a lot of time an awful lot of
effort as well and also like one of the
reasons why practice is so difficult for
people is because they don't know what
it what to do that people deep down
inside don't really know what to do so
they have faith and then if I do this
meditation if I do this technique if I
go through these motions then faith is
going to result in something but deep
down they don't see the connection
between doing this and wholesome doing
this and unwholesome which means they
don't know skillful is skillful
unskillful is unskillful it isn't it the
case how can you develop it if you don't
know what you want really if you don't
know what you're supposed to develop you
can't develop think so you want the mind
of loving-kindness understand what
loving-kindness is so when a person like
the example you give in a person has the
idea I want to have a mind of
loving-kindness instead of taking their
vague ambiguous not developed notion of
loving-kindness for granted and then
just try and emulate what
loving-kindness is in their mind they
should start questioning what they think
loving-kindness is that's how you
develop it you don't develop it by going
through some set of magical performances
and motions you develop it by
understanding it by by purifying your
understanding by clarifying your
understanding so if you ever thought I
want to be I want to have mine your
loving-kindness oh so I must speak slowly and smile and
oh so I must speak slowly and smile and
know I want to have a mind of
loving-kindness I must understand what loving-kindness
I must understand what loving-kindness
is when I do I will know how to protect
that theme I will know how to protect
that theme I will know how to advance it
how to develop it further
exactly and that's that the verse is it
loving kindness it is it's in a lobby
kind of shot he protects his mind like a
mother protects her only child that
protected sign to take the theme the
notion of the context of no niall will
you start developing in you protected so
you which means by developing the
context you already know what behavior is
you already know what behavior is
compatible with it what behavior isn't
but it in the case theme is developed
and held maintained you don't have to
really you don't have to worry about
your your actions exactly because that's
where you are yep yep that's what mean
you will have confidence then once you
studies earning the thing correctly
practicing mindfulness rightly you will
have confidence to know I don't need to
police my behavior as long as I police
my mind
police the root of my mind means nothing
bad can happen nothing bad that I can do
impossible impossible if situation
arises means you don't abandon your
context because the priority of that
which has been stolen for is more
important no the mind is the most
important the context is the most
important which means everything else is
second which means whatever befalls you
it will not give rise to lust or a
version or anything because you still
focus on protecting your mind
it doesn't fit exactly it's not
compatible yet so you get and you can
again like any suit the basic Lavery
suit is a theme in itself but that's I
mean like theme is not something you can
just just sort of well you can
particularize the team of something but
that particular those particular actions
particular things will have the meaning
only the basis of that general theme
it's not other way around
so really the practice would come down
instead of conceptualizing things you
should be contextualizing them you
should be looking at the context behind
your action not behind what is what is
I'm on a molecular level I'm moving my
hand moving my hand no no why why my
what is the reason what is my motivation
for moving my hand oh I want more food
am i hungry is it for desire and lust
what is the purpose of it that's where
you find the context
in this like like sort of fully focused
absorption into one moment know that
moment is already the result of the
context that you clearly not seen
because you're looking in the opposite
direction so the one pointedness of mind
is one pointedness of the unchangeable
context that induced despite of all this
particular action that are coming and
going not one point in and so I'm so one
not one point in and so I'm so one
pointed no other points exist for me
which is usually how people take
meditation to be but you could see like
if you wonder well which one's better
well ask yourself which one's more
likely to result in wisdom in what is
wisdom like say you got a wise man or
many wise men and what would be in
common to all and like you asked them
with different problems what would be in
common is that they have greater
perspective that's where you go to to
ask for an advice because you're gonna
get a better perspective because you are
locked onto the particular problem you
have and that's the definition of wisdom
development of perspective and what is
perspective other than greater context
you know you have a more particular
context but then you have the
fundamental universal context of
impermanence context of non ownership
context of suffering context of not self
fundamental universal included in
everything possible that has a nature of
being manifested it's as as broad as
general as universal as that someone so
developing the context means developing
perspective on things developing
perspective is nothing other than
developing wisdom and that's I mean you
ask yourself so will this practice of
developing context more likely result in
wisdom or practice of developing one
pointedness on a particular thing and
not give rise to anything else and you
don't really need to look far for the
answer totally ordered implied and
obvious myself before
I mean someone people asking that I want
to become a monk
so and then how should I do it should go
about this and what's the best thing to
do in a way exactly should I do it and
so on but the thing is you have to get
that theme of renunciation hmm give an
idea of renunciation and hold it there
yeah don't do anything unwholesome do
what is wholesome and just do that then
it doesn't really matter you don't to
worry about which monastry should I go
to how should wait you know yeah yes you
will be posting and you love your life
you realize then that circumstances of
your practice are exactly that
circumstantial oh they are contributing
towards the context I'm trying to
develop or they a bit too incompatible
and I feel like ordained in some crowd
that constantly busy tempo but that
would become apparent if you'll be
invested like clarifying the context of
what you want to do what you want to
develop that's what Buddha meant he goes and
that's what Buddha meant he goes and
listens to Wiseman he hears the advice
then he measures the task I said that
many times and something people always
overlook measuring the task means
understanding what needs to be done and
when you know what needs to be done you
will have inspiration to do it as well
but most people don't really know what
needs to be done so they end up doing
everything in nothing because they have
no criteria as in what what works what
doesn't but yes even just being a monk wearing a
but yes even just being a monk wearing a
robe we told earlier context that's why
back in the day when there when the
order started they had no rules they
were no rules because everybody
understanding Dhamma means and they
understood the context means they
already had that basis of wisdom which
means they would not do anything
incompatible so they were I mean they
were going pinned up at night eating in
the afternoon because none of that was
an issue but it's when context started
declining so then when new people would
come and hear the Dhamma they wouldn't
get the same level of context they
wouldn't have the same perspective on it
and then they would do things in the
directly contrary to the practice of
Dharma out of desire out of aversion out
of distraction and delusion and that's
where the rule started sort of
evolving okay don't do this don't do
this but in the beginning there was
nothing because there was no need for
anything to trust that's all it's a
trust context yes but you can only have
trust in the context once you at least
they have a degree of some discernment
of what the context is for example
likely if you trust in the context of
sensuality you can be guaranteed you'll
be going down sure yeah or if you you
don't even have to like like define
trust you can more like just welcome the
context of sensuality just not question
the context of sensuality we'll take it
for granted because sensuality ill will
distraction are basically context they
bring you the go with the grain of your
behavior in other words for somebody we
affected with ignorance those contexts
are effortless those contexts are
default so that's why initially have to
go against the grain in this integrated
context and start seeing the benefit in
the context of restraint context of non
Yeovil context of loving-kindness and so
on those are default they're effortless
so if you don't have the right context
you're automatically in the wrong
context but there is a context
absolutely that's why you're always
responsible for your actions
you always are that's why the mind comes
first because the context is the basis
for any action any significance any
meaning within it
so again on the content the theme of the
convex theme is funded the example I get
the other day when as I was in the
forest what I needed what I wanted to
have was a check hmm so I didn't have a
specific chain mind you know armrests
four migs whatever I just wanted this
general resting place chair something I
could rest my back so I had this image
in my the general chair hmm nothing
specific and I have that image in the
background in my mind just like you know
have the intention that's what I want
hmm it's clear to me what I want at the
feel okay but you're not actively
thinking chair and armrests no you just
had the purpose of the chair at the back
of your mind be you know oh man I felt
yeah I don't mean I'm not measuring now
hmm the places where I could sit in a
leveling ground I just have that con
that image background
hmm background sign with the intention
working and then my body's moving
because when there's an intention I want
to make change that the body's moving
whose eyes are scanning that's how all
the particular acts become intelligible
from the from the greater perspective of
the context that's why the mind is the
forerunner of all things now because my
mystical emerges somewhere else down the
horizon no it's because right there and
then while you're thinking that the
significance of your thoughts your
particular actions are already directed
by the mind by the context so you can
have particular context practical
context context rooted in this context
really that but fundamentally if you
start developing wisdom you're gonna
start discerning the universal context
and that's the most universal context is
suffering and being freedom from it
that's your goal that's your purpose
that's your practical dedication to free
myself from suffering once and for all
becomes a tool as it always is actually
even like when you are careless fully
engaging sensuality or will your body
can only be a tool for your expression
what for the belief of your expression
pretty much just the example of this so
my body's moving and I can see I'm
mindful of my eyes scan scanning and
within moments a perfect chain is
created without much particular thoughts
yeah cuz you had the purpose
peripherally and that kept everything
within those brackets of that
significance so whatever came came
through the brackets of practical
purpose of being seated down and resting
my back and the clear of the peripheral
purpose theme context is more accurately
more more efficiently you would find the
corresponding thing once those things
that that sign has been met
once that goal has been met in a general
sense the actual stop I don't now starts
polishing stones and making low yeah
exactly exactly
yeah that wasn't the point you have to
lose perspective in order to get in to
engage in their level and again again
that what would be the ultimate one of
the one of the most fundamental contexts
that is always implied in your life in
your actions in your particular feelings
perceptions on its death it's modern and
sati so while we are sitting here
talking at the back of my mind is the
context of death I will be I will die
maybe next moment maybe in 10 years time
doesn't matter but that context is
always there so whatever you choose to
do you have context of cessation implied
in it if you discern that context that's
why you you practice relinquishment
cessation as the Buddha will encourage
people not by throwing away your
particular things as LCI relinquished no
relinquishing basically your experience
on the basis of being susceptible to
death at any given time
that's a context that's already in it
you need the fundamental perspective
yeah well that I mean the chair was on a
more particular level it was depending
on your body your needs and Sonia
significance was implied by all these
other things but it's the same principle
whereby you want to take it to the point
of where you have no say about the
context you know say about impermanence
you have no say about death sickness
aging and that you have no saying that
that's why those are the universal as
the Buddha described them things are the
universal in every experience regardless
of your particular context particular
wisdom particular sort of actions and
inclinations these are thing in common
to all beings basically even if you're
not aware of it those principles remain
the same that's why the Buddha didn't
invent the Dhamma he rediscovered it so
the context you want to be dwelling on
if you want liberation is the context of
cessation cause why context of cessation
is incompatible with maintenance of
ownership of things that come on the
kind of your experience if your
experience is liable to death anything
that comes to your experience cannot be
appropriated in the same manner as if
you were to forget the you're liable to
death so ownership appropriation this is mine
so ownership appropriation this is mine
this is for me is in combat incompatible
with with I will die that's what people
who engage the whole life with following
the like ownership and desires and
sensuality are terrified at the
slightest implication of death because
it fully contradicts their being that
they've been nurturing and developing
being in the context of sensuality
proliferation and assumption of life so
that's what you don't have to go and
undo your particular ownership if you do
modern and oh sorry properly you will
disown your very senses yeah because you
value modern subtle you value it
contemplation of death clarification of
the theme of the inevitable guaranteed
cessation which means everything that's
incompatible with you will be abandoning
and that's again that there's similarly
that you heat up the pan whatever like
waterfalls on it it will dry you not
getting rid of the particular drops just
maintain the heat on the pan and
everything can stay on it same with fire
maintain the fire and don't worry what's
thrown into fire cuz it will burn if you
want to develop anything any skill any
wisdom any knowledge any recognition of
the principle an invention yet requires
that requires that greater perspective
requires that stepping back because if
all you see is what's in front of you
you're never gonna see beyond it and
purpose of what's in front of you is
already beyond it in a way like that the
chair doesn't have contain you sitting
on it you being seated on the chair
comfortably it's implied when you're not
seated in the chair so the purpose of
the thing you are trying to examine is
absent to that
present simultaneously whither thing but
present is a form of absence because
you're not actually as you said yourself
while you were looking for them for
something to emulate a chair to serve
the purpose that you wanted he was there
in the mind and you were doing all these
actions they were being directed by that
purpose by that context once you said he
was gone you fulfilled the purpose the
mind another thing has arisen another
mood another direction another context
but obviously there was a it was a more
particular type of theme but if you
develop these theme they depend on being
alive theme of impermanence that he was
modern under sati him of loving-kindness
basically depends for as long as there
is mind as long as there are five
aggregates yeah those things will stay
effortlessly for as long as the five
aggregates remain this idea and then
people who don't have the idea they'll
try to reverse-engineer it to emulate in
these particular notes but the true
genius or or oral wisdom or any form of
knowledge comes from that having the
greater perspective maintained in regard
to particular things you're doing
naturally because often people would
lose perspective once they start doing
things and that's like one of the main
may many the main characteristic of that
is sensuality sorry that is the main
characteristic of sensuality
that's what sensuality so bond with
ignorance because as soon as you engage
with sensuality you pretty much forget
about your desire of sensuality which is
why also people regard sensuality as a
way of satisfying your desire which as
we discussed before it's impossible
desire is on the level of the mind where
consent shall to be manifested on the
level of body and bodily actions which
means you need magical belief that this
corresponds to that as in these actions
will enable me to turn a blind eye to
still present desire in my mind
that's why you can never you can never
satisfy the desires and even people who
never made the effort to abandon desire
knows that deep down inside the desires
cannot be satisfied you maintain you you
maintaining the context by by losing the
sight of it and going elsewhere looking
for a solution apples and oranges
circuit so no matter how far your party
goes what it does it maintains the
conflict of desire yeah and the more you
ignore the context of desire the more
power start to exert over you that's why
the fever of sensuality grows the more
you engage with it acting we're doing
something sensual say sexual intercourse
everything particularly is yeah it's
fueled by the background I think you
remove the background thing all these
particular things become meaningless
even quite repulsive same with food like
you feel really really hungry hunger
overwhelmed your mind and then you're
just shoving things down your mouth just
like a wild anymore because you're
soaked you have completely lost the
sight of the context by the context is
so powerful influencing your behavior
that's where you want to be undoing the
context the themes of lust the themes of
ill-will resistance the themes of
carelessness distraction and you can't
undo them mechanically oh if you walk
like this talk like this sit like this
everything any unwholesome theme will be
uprooted from you know how can that be
because all all of those efforts are
aimed at the particular modes of
behavior then I've already secondary to
anything that's presently enduring but
if I teach you how to discern the theme
you see it for yourself
you don't need to worry about how you
sit how you work how you talk because
you are proof to the basis of desire for
those manifestations
to make sure that vehicles see when I
say you have to discern the theme in
order to develop it one of the
prerequisites for developing the right
view is discerned the mind which means
most people who - genus can't even
discern the mind as a phenomena as a
basic context all they can see what's in
front of yet whatever it's in front of
it it's meaningful because of the
peripheral because of that background
because of that context but that's
completely completely invisible to them
yes so that's why that's what I said
like if you start if you see if you stop
investing so much effort in
conceptualize and trying to like
informational is sort of clarify out -
this this particular movements in what
you should do and start looking at the
context of the very action of you
conceptualizing things right there and
then that's what like come back to the
present moment now just come back to the
mystical vague present moment but
discern the present context that takes
you away from the present moment isin
distracts you from it you come you are
in the present moment where you want to
be or not it's not optional you want to
discern the context that endures then
regardless of where your mind goes you
want to find Universal basis for it yes
so you you you'd and also it kind of
it's it's more ambiguous it's harder to
discern but actually in the long run
it's easier to do because it's not as
futile as just chasing concepts and
staying with like particularized aspects
of things
oh I'm breathing in like this and
breathing and I'm moving in as I speak
slowly I do this I'm controlling I'm
controlling I'm controlling now look at
the context look at the significance of
all these particular acts you become
aware of that you're automatically aware
of all these particular things so if you
are aware of your if you don't lose the
context for example they gives reason to
you eating food today means you won't be
eating food carelessly what is the
context for eating food in your present
situation oh it's for sustenance
oh it's for sustenance
the body removing the hunger but not
overdoing it not giving rise to censure
if that's the context but if you think
that context will be found in youtubing
food like three times per 10 seconds and
then I will swallow slowly and then I
will look up when I put food in my mouth
so I don't see what I'm put in my mouth
all that means you don't know where the
problem is the problem is not how you
eat the food or what you eat the problem
is your reason for eating is rooted in
lust or a version or whatever delusion
or all of it but if you maintain the
context the reason why you eat food you
know exactly when to stop and you
wouldn't care what you eat if it's
agreeable agreeable if it's disagreeable
you won't be sad about it either sure
sure go beyond that that's like the
first fetter that falls off once you
start developing countries properly like
I must be doing this now you see you
monkey there's nothing you must be doing
in a way because if there are certain
things you must be doing they will
automatically result in Habana then the
Buddha would have said so he would have
said that action particular action will
result in liberation but no he said that
any action result in more action good
action is better than bad action but
it's the election which means you can't
step outside of the domain of action
while you keep performing action so
first you replace bad action with good
action but then you want to develop the
universal context theme of non last not
a version on distraction towards any
action and that's how you feel self of
virtue and duty from from expression of
last aversion delusion all of it that's
how become another hunt aaron has the
ultimate empirical context of
impermanence that has saturated him
thoroughly there is nothing that he can
ever appropriate again regard his mind
mine you want to develop the principle
and you will see it working because you
will be unable to suffer amid suffering
so how can you not suffer amidst the
particular suffering because it's the
context to give suffering no particular
things they give suffering to the
context if suffering were truly coming
from external things particular things
you wouldn't be able to feel so from it
that's why IRA Hahn who is freed himself
fundamentally from the context of
suffering he says oh the only
disturbance disturbance that is left is
on account of these five aggregates but
even that will go when I in the body
breaks apart so he doesn't refer to only
suffering that's left no it disturbance
that's left all this annoyance this left
is only but for putana annoyance is
suffering because he hasn't developed
the context that that frees him from
suffering fundamentally and then he
can't suffer um it's all these things
they used to they used to kind of
reverse so to speak their order whereby
instead of realizing the suffering comes
from your mind that's where you that's
it's your craving in your mind in regard
to the circumstances that's making you
suffer not having that perspective not
having the Four Noble Truths you would
then think that these particular things
that's why you suffer that's why there
is suffering in my mind because this
happened that I didn't want to happen
whatever happens that's not the root for
suffering the root of suffering is
craving in your mind in regard to
whatever happens and craving in a way
it's already a form of context that
people are unaware of you are unaware
that it's you who induce the suffering
by wanting more of pleasure or less of
this pleasure or wanting to just ignore
the neutral that's on the level of the
mind
what is it you know please in training
poses what is it supposed to be like
yeah obviously you need for such a
universal context you need Buddha's
instruction because if you find your way
out of suffering by yourself well you
will be either some assembler Pacheco
Buddha but good news is you don't have
to find it by yourself because down we
still out there but you want to see that
suffering does it nobody says you
deserve what comes your way in terms of
circumstances no there's nothing to do
with it but you suffering on account of
whatever comes your way in regard to
circumstances that's on you suffering is
your own doing and because of that you
can actually free yourself to the point
where you gonna set himself even if the
highway robbers pin you down and start
sowing your limbs one by one savagely
you won't have your will towards them
because you won't be suffering on
account of it it's going to be extreme
disturbance extremely disagreeable but
not it cannot reverse that order and
take over the context of the mind that
has been liberated from it it's
impossible no amount of pressure of this
agreeable can become can induce craving
to get rid of it because craving always
comes from the mind
and if you have relinquished the
ownership of that mind what is there to
resist what is there to defend what is
there to crave against